<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Paw Store</string>
    <string name="tulisan">INPUT TEXT HERE</string>
    <string name="openingtoy">Take playtime outside or in with Paw dog toys. Shop the best dog toys for puppies and dogs, a wide variety perfect for your pup favorite style of play.</string>
    <string name="openingfood">Find a great selection of top dog food brands for your pet. Use our guide to different dog foods, including grain free, organic and natural.</string>
    <string name="openingclothing">Keep your pet looking fashionable with the latest dog clothes, shoes and apparel. From dresses and jumpers, to hoodies and bows.</string>
    <string name="openingaccesories">We offer a huge selection of the newest dog accessories by all your favorite dog designers</string>
    <string name="pedigree">Pedigree food main ingredient consists of Corn, and Corn does not add much significant value for a dog’s nutrition. We can ignore nutrition of Corn as it is very minimal.The second ingredient of Pedigree dog food is Poultry by-products. Poultry by-products can contain anything from feet, beaks, undeveloped eggs apart from the real meat like chicken breast or wings or legs. The advantage of this is the by-products give around 300% of more protein than fresh poultry.</string>
    <string name="cesar">Cesar food main ingredient consists of Corn, and Corn does not add much significant value for a dog’s nutrition. We can ignore nutrition of Corn as it is very minimal.The second ingredient of Pedigree dog food is Poultry by-products. Poultry by-products can contain anything from feet, beaks, undeveloped eggs apart from the real meat like chicken breast or wings or legs. The advantage of this is the by-products give around 300% of more protein than fresh poultry.</string>
    <string name="eukanoba">Eukanoba food main ingredient consists of Corn, and Corn does not add much significant value for a dog’s nutrition. We can ignore nutrition of Corn as it is very minimal.The second ingredient of Pedigree dog food is Poultry by-products. Poultry by-products can contain anything from feet, beaks, undeveloped eggs apart from the real meat like chicken breast or wings or legs. The advantage of this is the by-products give around 300% of more protein than fresh poultry.</string>
    <string name="iams">Iams food main ingredient consists of Corn, and Corn does not add much significant value for a dog’s nutrition. We can ignore nutrition of Corn as it is very minimal.The second ingredient of Pedigree dog food is Poultry by-products. Poultry by-products can contain anything from feet, beaks, undeveloped eggs apart from the real meat like chicken breast or wings or legs. The advantage of this is the by-products give around 300% of more protein than fresh poultry.</string>
    <string name="purina">Purina food main ingredient consists of Corn, and Corn does not add much significant value for a dog’s nutrition. We can ignore nutrition of Corn as it is very minimal.The second ingredient of Pedigree dog food is Poultry by-products. Poultry by-products can contain anything from feet, beaks, undeveloped eggs apart from the real meat like chicken breast or wings or legs. The advantage of this is the by-products give around 300% of more protein than fresh poultry.</string>
    <string name="royal">Royal food main ingredient consists of Corn, and Corn does not add much significant value for a dog’s nutrition. We can ignore nutrition of Corn as it is very minimal.The second ingredient of Pedigree dog food is Poultry by-products. Poultry by-products can contain anything from feet, beaks, undeveloped eggs apart from the real meat like chicken breast or wings or legs. The advantage of this is the by-products give around 300% of more protein than fresh poultry.</string>
</resources>
